quiz_data = [
    {
        "question": "The way that files are located on disk is by their path",
        "choices": ["True", "False", "Maybe", "Kinda"],
        "answer": "True"
    },
    {
        "question": "How are dictionaries declared in python?",
        "choices": ["Using square brackets[]", "Using curly braces{}", "Using parentheses()", "Using angle brackets<>"],
        "answer": "Using curly braces{}"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the keyword used to refer to the current instance of a class in Python?",
        "choices": ["this", "self", "current", "Obj"],
        "answer": "self"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the purpose of an init method in a class?",
        "choices": ["To define class-level variables", "To initialize", "Set an object attributes to its default state",
                    "To create a new instance of the class"],
        "answer": "To initialize"
    },
    {
        "question": "The ==operator test for deep equality only",
        "choices":  ["True", "False", "Maybe", "No"],
        "answer": "False"

    },
    {
        "question": "What is the style of programming that GUI's utilize?",
        "choices": ["Top-down design", "Object-oriented programming", "Event-driven programming",
                    "Functional Programming"],
        "answer": "Event-driven programming"

    },
    {
        "question": "What is not a layout manager?",
        "choices":  ["Place", "Pack", "Grid", "Coordinate"],
        "answer": "Coordinate"

    },
    {
        "question": "Which college do the creators of this quiz attend?",
        "choices":  ["Berea College", "Vanderbilt", "College of the Ozarks", "Colby"],
        "answer": "Berea College"

    },
    {
        "question": "What is the best way to create an exception?",
        "choices":  ["The raise command", "The def command", "Utilizing the else/elif commands", "All of the above"],
        "answer": "The raise command"

    },
    {
        "question": "To use a file you must first use which of the functions?",
        "choices": ["Open", "Read", "Scan", "Readline"],
        "answer": "Open"

    }

]